export const pythonRecursionAssignment = {
  title: 'Python Recursion â€“ Assignment',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What does a recursive function call?',
      options: ['Another function', 'Main function', 'Itself', 'Loop'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which case stops recursion?',
      options: ['Recursive case', 'Base case', 'Else case', 'Default case'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Recursion uses which data structure?',
      options: ['Queue', 'Array', 'Stack', 'List'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Which is a classic recursive problem?',
      options: ['Sorting', 'Factorial', 'Searching', 'Input'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Recursive call must move toward?',
      options: ['Start', 'Loop', 'Base case', 'End'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which is faster in general?',
      options: [
        'Recursion',
        'Loops',
        'Both same',
        'Depends on compiler',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Recursion is best suited for?',
      options: [
        'Repetitive tasks',
        'Hierarchical data',
        'Simple printing',
        'Input handling',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which problem uses recursion naturally?',
      options: [
        'Binary tree traversal',
        'Addition',
        'Printing',
        'Assignment',
      ],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Too much recursion can cause?',
      options: [
        'Syntax error',
        'Memory overflow',
        'Type error',
        'Compilation error',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Recursion improves?',
      options: [
        'Readability',
        'Problem solving',
        'Logic clarity',
        'All',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
  ],
}